

MARKEL ZUBIZARRETA

DIGITAL DESIGN & DIGITAL MARKETING

PROFILE

Digital Marketing and Graphic Design Specialist with a high interest in developing my career around creative areas. I am passionate about communication, digital design, social media and e-commerce.

Currently working on a UX/UI design project to improve my company's website and app.

EDUCATION

EAE BUSINESS SCHOOL, MASTER'S DEGREE

DIGITAL MARKETING AND ECOMMERCE / 2019 - 2020

Minor in Neuromarketing.

UPV/EHU UNIVERSITY, BACHELOR'S DEGREE

ADVERTISING & PR / 2012 - 2016

Minor in Digital Design

SKILLS

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE

MICROSOFT OFFICE

MAILCHIMP

GOOGLE ANALYTICS/ADS

WORDPRESS/PRESTASHOP

FIGMA

LANGUAGES

- **SPANISH**, mother tongue
 - ENGLISH, C1 ■

CERTIFICATIONS

- BRANDING COURSE, 2019 ■
- COMMUNITY MANAGER COURSE. 2018

CONTACT

+34 610 80 74 89

markelzubi@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/markelzubizarreta

Madrid

EXPERIENCE

DIGGIA GROUP

DIGITAL MARKETING & DIGITAL DESIGN SPECIALIST / 2020 - NOW

- Design of online and print creativities, print adds, leaflets, posters, social media graphic content.
- · Elaboration and design of catalogs and corporate magazine.
- Design of documentation, memories, data, presentations, merchandising and large format: vinyls, stands, displays, rollups, etc.
- Web/App Design: image optimization, graphics, banners, newsletters, emailing and UX/UI design.
- Branding and corporate design. Elaboration of brandbook and definition and delimitation of brand graphic elements.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Final arts and coordination of external services.
- Graphic design for social media, banners and visuals for website and social ads.
- \cdot Designing Marketing Campaigns and Actions.

MAPFRE

GRAPHIC DESIGN SPECIALIST / 2018 - 2019

- Development of infographics and graphic diagrams for dissemination on web platforms. Making presentations. Photo editing
- Participation in the creative process to devise different content and publications.
- · Collaboration in the definition of Branding Strategies.
- Collaboration in the publication of content and creativities in social networks with the Communication Department.

FEDERACIÓN VIZCAÍNA DE GOLF

GRAPHIC DESIGN SPECIALIST

/ 2017 - 2018

Performing graphic design tasks for web, business cards, brochures, etc. using Illustrator and Photoshop.